maxuearn.com 2010-03-25

# Maximize Your Earnings » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at my site <http://www.maxuearn.com/> . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage users to be aware when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Project Wonderful, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact me **maxuearn@gmail.com**.

By Alexa.
